Guide to the Broadway Preview Series records, 1986-1993 UA.24.40.0051
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Broadway Preview Series records
1986-1993
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Broadway Preview Series.
UA.24.40.0051
3.7 Linear Feet 2250 items
From 1986-1993, the Broadway Preview Series premiered new works for the American theater at Duke. The first Broadway Preview performance staged in the Reynolds Industries Theater (March 10, 1986) was Emanuel Azenberg's Broadway production of Eugene O'Neill's Long Day's Journey Into Night, starring Jack Lemmon and Kevin Spacey. Some of the other productions previewed at Duke are: Broadway Bound and Laughter on the 23rd Floor by Neil Simon; A Month of Sundays with Jason Robards; A Walk in the Woods with Sam Waterston; Metamorphosis with Mikhail Baryshnikov; The Circle with Rex Harrison; Artist Descending a Staircase by Tom Stoppard; and Lucifer's Child with Julie Harris. The work of the Broadway Preview Series is continued today by Theater Previews at Duke. Collection contains programs, clippings, photographs, some autograph notes, and other materials pertaining to productions. Also includes scripts. The material ranges in date from 1986-1993.
Historical note
From 1986-1993, the Broadway Preview Series premiered new works for the American theater at Duke. The first Broadway Preview performance staged in the Reynolds Industries Theater (March 10, 1986) was Emanuel Azenberg's Broadway production of Eugene O'Neill's Long Day's Journey Into Night, starring Jack Lemmon and Kevin Spacey. Some of the other productions previewed at Duke are: Broadway Bound and Laughter on the 23rd Floor by Neil Simon; A Month of Sundays with Jason Robards; A Walk in the Woods with Sam Waterston; Metamorphosis with Mikhail Baryshnikov; The Circle with Rex Harrison; Artist Descending a Staircase by Tom Stoppard; and Lucifer's Child with Julie Harris. The work of the Broadway Preview Series is continued today by Theater Previews at Duke.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Collection Overview
Collection contains programs, clippings, photographs, some autograph notes, and other materials pertaining to productions. Also includes scripts. The material ranges in date from 1986-1993.
Provenance
The Broadway Preview Series Records were received by Duke University Archives as a transfer in 1992 and 2004.
Duke University. Department of Theater Studies; Duke University--Students; Duke University. Theatre Previews at Duke; Duke University. Broadway Preview Series -- History; Duke University. Broadway Preview Series.
- Broadway Preview Series records
  - "The Merry Wives of Windsor Texas" "1492" See also Films Made at Duke University, 1989 1992 (Box 1)
  - Duke University Union Drama Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Neil Simon "Broadway Bound." Script, Autograph Notes, Clippings, Programs, Publicity, Photographs, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Drama Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Office Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Programs and Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - "Long Day's Journey Into Night", 1986 (Box 2)
  - "A Month of Sundays", 1987 (Box 2)
  - "An Evening with Waylon Jennings", 1987 (Box 2)
  - "A Walk In the Woods", 1988 (Box 2)
  - "1492" by Christopher Bishop, 1992 (Box 2)
  - 1971-1972 Season (Box 2)
  - 1972-1973 Season (Box 2)
  - 1973-1974 Season (Box 2)
  - 1974-1975 Season (Box 2)
  - 1975-1976 Season (Box 2)
  - 1979-1980 Season (Box 2)
  - Office Receipts, 1970-1976 (Box 2)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Financial, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Gala Information, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Budget, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Institute of the Arts Residency Activities, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Gala Info and Ticket Forms, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Publicity Ads, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Tickets, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Hospitality, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Contacts, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Publicity, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Publicity Materials, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Schedule, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Technical and Dressing Rooms, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Ushers Student Assistants, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Students, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Schedule, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Playbill, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night." Photographs, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Contacts, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Dressing Rooms, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Publicity and Advertising, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Pictures, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Schedule, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Interns, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Cast Parking, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Playbill, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Publicity, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Schedule, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound." Budget, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Broadway Bound.", September-October 1986 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Pig Roast, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Fundraising, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Interns, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Publicity, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Financial, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "A Month of Sundays." Cast Photos, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - "Waylon Jennings." Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Waylon Jennings." Photos, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Waylon Jennings." Tickets, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "A Walk in the Woods." Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "A Walk in the Woods." Photos, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "My Heart Belongs to Daddy." Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "Metamorphosis." Photos, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Metamorphosis." Press Reviews, Publicity, Playbill, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Metamorphosis." Ralph Roseman (Producer) Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Metamorphosis." General File, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Plays. General File, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Plays. Interns, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Moonlight and Valentino." Press and Publicity, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Moonlight and Valentino." Ellen Simon Clipping, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Moonlight and Valentino." Photos, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "The Circle" Photos. (Box 3)
  - "Artist Descending a Staircase." Photos, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Artist Descending a Staircase." Intern Applications, 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Merry Wives of Windsor, Texas", 1989 (Box 3)
  - "Avner the Eccentric", 1990 (Box 3)
  - "Lucifer's Child." Julie Harris, 1990 (Box 3)
  - "Lucifer's Child." Photos, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Broadway Preview Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - "1492." General File, 1992 (Box 3)
  - "1492." Photos, 1992 (Box 3)
  - "Laughter." Photos, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1986-1992 (Box 4)
  - "1492" Score, 1992 (Box 4)
  - "1492." Videotape, 1992 (Box 4)